cya on ewy censored and i need to go
ahead and share a public comment
that was left on my
recent video
and i'm sharing this comment with
everybody because this was a person that
was a guest on my channel
several times a few years ago
and then this person did a 180 and
started slandering me
and um i don't know what happened
um
it it was very odd
but
it's happened over the years where i've
seen people do 180s
and um let me go and share this comment
that he left it's not just towards me
but it's towards everyone
in the community who sees the bible
changes
and so i really am sending this out to
warn you about this person
who left a public comment on my channel
and this is how i'm choosing to respond
is publicly
so
here is the message and i will show you
his channel in just a minute and so i
can tell you who this person is
um this was
his
comment in response to another comment
that somebody left
i answered your first question in one of
my videos on my channel but be sure that
those attacking you are not following
what they should be following
after founding the bible is tainted
so no
they are not following jesus alone
number one
because jesus did not know them out of
their rejection of repentance for the
new sins
and slandering brothers and sisters
repeatedly over youtube
well right there i'm going to comment
that
i
have rarely
mentioned or called out
anyone on my channel i've done it less
than a handful of times
with good reason
but for the most part i've often said if
you guys remember i will give no names
in this instance i am
exposing this person not exposing i'm
sharing who he is because he left a
public comment
and now he's
slandering
or i should say he's committing libel
right because he's putting in print
about everyone in the
um
everyone who sees the bible changes
he goes on to say
and also because they lack wisdom many
of them are hypocrites having double
lives and even no testimony in jesus at
all
i i really don't know where he's getting
this information because we are all
about on this channel and my previous
channels of people giving testimony
of what jesus christ has done in their
lives
and i've shared with you my testimony
not in depth but i have shared with you
over the years he goes on to say many
others inside this cult
insult people like if it is not being
written on the books by angels in
heavens
so basically they cannot accuse you of
not being a christian when in god's eyes
they are not even christians
especially the queen
of the windella heavens eya that's me
who knew i had that title but now i know
that's how he refers me which is
so weird right really weird and rather
creepy
she is not a christian and that is a
fact in jesus eyes she cannot erase her
sin in his face one day in the future
well what does it mean to be a christian
i follow jesus christ as my lord and
savior the son of god the king of kings
and lord of lords
he's the one i follow
he goes on to say i'm an ex-catholic but
i'm not rejecting anyone because of
their current faith
as i know that the ones last called to
the king's banquet are from the streets
and corners of the world because
precisely those formerly invited make
their own excuses to not attend
distracting themselves in silly matters
that ruined their salvation
let me go ahead and move i took another
screenshot which is here and he goes on
to say amos famine is not prophesying
the bible changes
is prophesying the famine over the
hearing
which happened so long ago
i also explained in the two hour long
video step aside oh and then i guess
that's another thought and he said step
aside from the eye channels and wolves
my advice don't reply don't come back to
look unless the holy spirit directs you
directly tells you so and who am i to
believe that just because you are
catholic you are not having
communication with the holy spirit as i
myself had before exiting that religion
there is too much proud in the windell
effect community
they believe they are the chosen remnant
when they are the five stupid virgins
that's what god corroborates anyone
testing spirits over this cult and
believe me i'm aware the bible is
tainted
but it isn't relevant what you discover
but what you do after discovering it
blessings brother
so this is his channel
i went to it didn't know who he was when
i read that comment
edpv
and i scroll down
and lo and behold i discover
that it's eddie
or vinceador
and this person has been a guest on my
channel
several times
and the last time i think was you know
um
several years ago a few at least a
couple of years ago
and what happened is that he
started writing malicious
comments
in
the live chat
and then he would leave post posts
comments that were disparaging
and i blocked him
and then eddie
contacted me and he he
was expressed
repentance
in the live chat with a new name
and he wanted to share something so i
unblocked him
and now he's at it again
you know
eddie
i don't even know how to even respond to
your comment because there's so many
accusations that are
here and all i can tell you is that i
forgive you
i forgive you brother
because you are deceived
and
yes it's extremely important how we live
our lives to live a life of holiness
in christ
and it's also critically important that
we share
not only the truth that's found in jesus
christ
critically important
and something that i do all the time on
my channel
and i also warn people of the satanic
bible changes because so few people are
doing it
if you know the bible is supernaturally
satanically changed why are you not
warning people
why
there is no good reason
to not share in fact brother i now
remember what happened at least one of
the issues
i was encouraging you who speaks spanish
to testify on your own channel
about the satanic bible changes and you
said no
i remember that
i remember saying that to you
and you said no
my question is
why would you not want to share
about the bible changes
it makes you complicit
in the nefarious wicked satanic changes
but again i will say
i forgive you for
your accusations
and coming against this community and i
do so publicly
because your comment
was public
and with that said
again
i forgive you